[
  {
    "question": "Hi!",
    "response": "Hello! How may I assist you today?",
    "action": "none"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to report a problem with BloatynosyAI #reddit #help #issue #github",
    "response": "AI on it! ðŸš€ #BugBuster",
    "action": "https://www.reddit.com/search/?q=bloatynosy&type=comment&sort=new"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I add my Microsoft Account?",
    "response": "Sure, I'll guide you. Opening Account settings...",
    "action": "ms-settings:privacy-accountinfo"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to create a PIN",
    "response": "Sure, let me help. Opening Sign-in settings...",
    "action": "ms-settings:signinoptions"
  },
  {
    "question": "Check for Windows updates",
    "response": "Sure, I'll check for updates. Checking for updates...",
    "action": "ms-settings:windowsupdate"
  },
   {
    "question": "I want to change my Wallpaper",
    "response": "Sure, a Windows desktop should reflect your personality. Let us change it.",
    "action": "changeWallpaper"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to adjust the appearance and performance of Windows",
    "response": "Sure, Let us switch to the Performance Options",
    "action": "SystemPropertiesPerformance.exe"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to switch between dark and light Windows mode",
    "response": "Let us join the dark or light side...",
    "action": "toggleThemeMode"
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I restore backups?",
    "response": "Certainly! Opening Appcopier...",
    "action": "openFile",
    "appPath": "packages\\Appcopier\\Appcopier.exe"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to create a Restore point",
    "response": "Now you are on the safe side. Restore point has been created.",
    "action": "createRestorePoint",
    "powershellCommand": "$desc = 'BloatynosyAI Restore'; Checkpoint-Computer -Description \"$desc\" -RestorePointType \"Modify_Settings\""
  },
  {
    "question": "How can I reset my system?",
    "response": "Resetting your PC lets you perform a clean reinstallation and update of Windows while keeping your personal data and most Windows settings intact.",
    "action": "runSystemReset"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to clean up my storage",
    "response": "Running intelligent Storage Sense.",
    "action": "runStorageSense"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is my Windows version?",
    "response": "You are on Build: [buildNumber]",
    "action": "showWindowsVersion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Display my systems available disk space",
    "response": "Available space on your system partition:",
    "action": "showDiskSpace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Take screenshot #SnippingTool",
    "response": "Screenshot captured and send to clipboard.",
    "action": "takeScreenshot"
  },
  {
    "question": "Show apps that start with Windows",
    "response": "Opening Task Manager to the autostart tab.",
    "action": "switchToAutostartTab"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to uninstall an App",
    "response": "Opening the Windows Apps Uninstaller...",
    "action": "openWindowsAppsUninstaller"
  },
  {
    "question": "Show Processes with High RAM Usage",
    "response": "Listing processes with high RAM usage...",
    "action": "showHighRamProcesses"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to run a quick scan in Windows Defender Security",
    "response": "Running Windows Defender quick scan...",
    "action": "runWindowsDefenderScan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Give me a sneak peek of Chris Titus tool in action #plugin",
    "response": "Interpreting PowerShell script...",
    "action": "runPowerShellScript",
    "scriptPath": "research\\ChrisTitusAppHandler.ps1"
  },
  {
    "question": "Help me remove the Microsoft OneDrive app #plugin",
    "response": "Interpreting PowerShell script...",
    "action": "runPowerShellScript",
    "scriptPath": "research\\OneDriveHandler.ps1"
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to install an app #winget",
    "response": "Switching to apps section...",
    "action": "installApps",
  },
  {
    "question": "I want to uninstall bloatware appx packages",
    "response": "Switching to crapware section...",
    "action": "uninstallAppx",
  },
  {
    "question": "I want set up my my system and privacy settings",
    "response": "Switching to privacy dashboard...",
    "action": "privacyDashboard",
  },
   {
    "question": "Restart Windows Explorer (Along With the Taskbar and Start Menu)",
    "response": "Restarting explorer.exe...",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"taskkill /f /im explorer.exe && start explorer.exe"
  },
   {
	"question": "Change Taskbar alignment to the left",
	"response": "Taskbar has been aligned to left.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarAl /t REG_DWORD /d 0 /f"
   },
    {
	"question": "Change Taskbar alignment to the center",
	"response": "Taskbar has been aligned to center.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarAl /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f"
   },
    {
	"question": "Add the Widgets Button on the Taskbar",
	"response": "Let us enable the Widgets.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarDa /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f"
   },
    {
	"question": "Remove the Widgets Button on the Taskbar",
	"response": "Let us disable the Widgets button.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v TaskbarDa /t REG_DWORD /d 0 /f"
   },
   {
	"question": "Remove AI in Taskbar (Copilot Button) #ai",
	"response": "Copilot Button in Taskbar has been disabled.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Microsoft\\Windows\\CurrentVersion\\Explorer\\Advanced /v ShowCopilotButton /t REG_DWORD /d 0 /f"
   },
   {
	"question": "Remove AI Icon in Microsoft Edge #ai",
	"response": "Copilot Button in Edge has been disabled.",
	"action": "shell",
	"command":"reg add HKEY_CURRENT_USER\\Software\\Policies\\Microsoft\\Windows /v TurnOffWindowsCopilot /t REG_DWORD /d 1 /f"
   },
   {
	 "question": "Disable Copilot Pro ads on Windows 11 #vivetool",
	 "response": "ViveTool action performed successfully.",
	 "action": "viveTool",
	 "viveCommand": "disable",
	 "viveFeatureId": "47942561",
	 "viveBuildAvailability": "This is hidden in the latest Windows 11 Dev and Beta builds."
	},
	{
    "question": "Translate the UI of this app into German #deutsch #update",
    "response": "Ava says: Kindly click the refresh button to apply the recent changes. This might be an AI-powered translation, where errors cannot be ruled out.",
    "action": "translate",
     "downloadUri": {
     "frontend.html": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Bloatynosy/main/Localization/DE/frontend.html",
     "staticAIData.json": "https://raw.githubusercontent.com/builtbybel/Bloatynosy/main/Localization/DE/staticAIData.json"
		}
	}
]